<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Southwest Economic Solutions on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/southwest-economic-solutions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Southwest Economic Solutions on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:55:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/southwest-economic-solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2018 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for the annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
The event is generously supported by Quicken Loans and Fifth Third Bank.
5:30-7 PM: ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Showcase &amp;amp; Strolling Dinner 7-8:30 PM: Annual Convening Celebration Event Highlights:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Fall Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for a fall celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. We had an incredible time hosting entrepreneurs, community stakeholders, and advocates at this year&amp;rsquo;s annual event, so we wanted to create another opportunity for our partners and participants to come together and celebrate. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Walter Winesberry, Maximize Autistic Potential</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/19/people-of-prosperus-walter-winesberry-maximize-autistic-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 14:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/19/people-of-prosperus-walter-winesberry-maximize-autistic-potential/</guid>
      <description>This is the fourth post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Walter Winesberry, the owner of Maximize Autistic Potential. “[My business is called] Maximize Autistic Potential. Over the last 11 years, through trial and error, we’ve come up with a completely natural protocol that diminishes autism symptoms in children. We’ve been helping families for about the last 10 years. I have a degree in biology which helps me look at what doctors and scientists are saying about what is happening in the bodies of children with autism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chanell Scott Contreras is New ProsperUS Director</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/05/chanell-scott-contreras-is-new-prosperus-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/05/chanell-scott-contreras-is-new-prosperus-director/</guid>
      <description>Chanell Scott Contreras is the new director of Southwest Solutions’ ProsperUS Detroit program. Chanell takes over the role held by Kimberly Faison, who left to become program officer at the Ralph C. Wilson, Jr. Foundation. Kimberly had led ProsperUS since it began in 2012, and developed it into a premier program to train and support ethnic and immigrant entrepreneurs wanting to establish small businesses in Detroit neighborhoods.
“I am inspired by ProsperUS’ place-based approach to equitable economic development, and am honored and thrilled to join the ProsperUS team of talented and dedicated individuals who have an incredible track record of assisting aspiring small business owners in the city,” said Chanell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for an annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. This year, we&amp;rsquo;re especially excited to host a pitch competition sponsored by Fifth Third Bank following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
Details: May 11, 2017, from 5-8 PM The Jam Handy 2900 E. Grand Blvd. Detroit, MI 48202</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
