<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Lunch Stop on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/the-lunch-stop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Lunch Stop on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:04:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/the-lunch-stop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Fall Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for a fall celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. We had an incredible time hosting entrepreneurs, community stakeholders, and advocates at this year&amp;rsquo;s annual event, so we wanted to create another opportunity for our partners and participants to come together and celebrate. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap: 2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening and Pitch Competition</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/05/12/recap-2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-and-pitch-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/05/12/recap-2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-and-pitch-competition/</guid>
      <description>The ProsperUS Detroit team was thrilled by the outpouring of support and enthusiasm for the program and its entrepreneurs at its fifth annual event celebrating small businesses learning to grow in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Thanks to WillUParty Event Planning, Featherstone Moments for photographing the night, Three Lyons Creative for capturing video, Jam Handy for hosting, and to Fifth Third Bank for their generous financial support of the evening&amp;rsquo;s festivities!
  Photos courtesy of Juan Carlos Perez of Featherstone Moments:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
