<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Impact Story on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/impact-story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Impact Story on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 18:40:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/impact-story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Lesa Walker</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/27/people-of-prosperus-lesa-walker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/27/people-of-prosperus-lesa-walker/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Lesa Walker By: Torisa Johnson  Lesa Walker grew up in Canada, and has lived in Detroit for her adult life. Growing up in a large family with nine siblings, Walker spent lots of quality time early in life experimenting with deserts and competing against her siblings. Walker’s fond memories of making cow patties alongside them influenced the name of her business, Sweet Thoughts. Appropriately named, Sweet Thoughts is a dessert business selling various forms of delicious chocolate and dessert chips, additionally offering healthy yet sweet options that still manage to be delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Enid Parham</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/people-of-prosperus-enid-parham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 18:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/people-of-prosperus-enid-parham/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Enid Parham By: Torisa Johnson A chef all of her life, Detroit native Enid Parham puts a twist on food by combining her passion for cooking with her love for cannabis. After lots of careful research on the topic, including testing groups, Parham started her business, Lucky Pistil, in 2016. Lucky Pistil is a far cry from traditional cannabis edibles found in dispensaries. Parham’s dishes and catering services are gourmet dishes with up-scale food and service, though she does offer the option of casual settings as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Lea Addington</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/13/people-of-prosperus-lea-addington/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 19:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/13/people-of-prosperus-lea-addington/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Lea Addington By: Mackenzie Hewitt  Born and raised in metro-Detroit, Lea Addington began her business, LIT Vegan Kitchen, in 2017. Addington had been vegan for several months when one of her family members reached out to her seeking help transitioning their diet due to medical reasons. After Addington began to notice the positive changes as a result of her vegan diet, she decided to share this with her community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Mayra Planas</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/06/people-of-prosperus-mayra-planas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/06/people-of-prosperus-mayra-planas/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Mayra Planas By: Torisa Johnson Mayra Planas moved from Miami to Detroit with her family in 2002. Born and raised in Cuba, Miami resembled home in language and climate, but Detroit was a completely different scene. Planas tried to go back to Miami for two years, but in the end was glad she stayed, as she developed a love for both the city and the people. The idea to start her company, Havana on Wheels, came to Planas in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Le’Genevieve Squires &amp; Brittiany Peeler</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/30/people-of-prosperus-legenevieve-squires-brittiany-peeler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 21:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/30/people-of-prosperus-legenevieve-squires-brittiany-peeler/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Le’Genevieve Squires &amp;amp; Brittiany Peeler  By: Mackenzie Hewitt Detroit natives Brittiany Peeler and Le’Genevieve Squires formalized their business, Experience Relish, in 2018. After attending college, the pair moved backed to Detroit in 2016. At the time, Experience Relish was only a hobby that involved cooking for family and friends, but their fresh take on childhood dishes began to spread quickly by word of mouth. They decided to gain knowledge about becoming a catering company, and they attended Detroit Start-Up Week and Skill Share Classes at FoodLab that same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Whitney &amp; Jeremy Lewis</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/23/people-of-prosperus-whitney-jeremy-lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 18:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/23/people-of-prosperus-whitney-jeremy-lewis/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Whitney and Jeremy Lewis By Mackenzie Hewitt Whitney and Jeremy Lewis were both born and raised in Detroit, MI, and returned in 2016 after leaving temporarily for college. Two foodies with a drive for entrepreneurship, the couple launched Boiling Point Detroit in 2019, inspired by the unique dining experience of a seafood boil. After cooking for family and friends initially, the couple branched out to host events. When their service was well received by the public, they knew Boiling Point would take off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Jamie Hendrix</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/01/people-of-prosperus-jamie-hendrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 17:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/01/people-of-prosperus-jamie-hendrix/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Jamie Hendrix By: Anna Gotskind BeHer is a women’s clothing store that offers a variety of tops, bottoms, one-pieces, and dresses in sizes ranging from small to plus-sized. Based in Morningside Detroit, BeHer specializes in urban street style and transitional all-day wear allowing customers to wear the pieces both to work as well as any evening event after.
 Jamie Hendrix, the founder of BeHer, started out wanting to restore a storefront in her community of Morningside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Simmons Family</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/25/people-of-prosperus-simmons-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 16:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/25/people-of-prosperus-simmons-family/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: The Simmons Family By: Weyman Cohen Tag Team Autoworks is a collision shop specializing in detailing. Tag Team Autoworks (TTA) has an office that does government contracts. There is a division of the business that goes into housing and urban development. **The Simmons family mission **is to get the collision shop up and running. Gerald, having suffered dozens of heart attacks, serves his family as a teacher of business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Shayla Davis</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/15/people-of-prosperus-shayla-davis-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 16:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/15/people-of-prosperus-shayla-davis-2/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Shayla Davis By: Anna Gotskind Unik I Am strives to empower and uplift young women to embrace their journey and not let mistakes define who they are. Founder, Shayla Davis, accomplishes this through motivational speaking about her own experiences and providing support services to help women find housing, jobs, and more.
Unik I Am&amp;rsquo;s mission is to seek to uplift, empower, and motivate women to understand and embrace their struggles, success, failures, mistakes, and achieve their goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: E.J. Wells</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/08/people-of-prosperus-e-j-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 18:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/08/people-of-prosperus-e-j-wells/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: E.J. Wells By: Weyman Cohen LightsUp Entertainment’s mission is to provide quality and personal production value to your event using lighting, sound and production professionals to make your vision come to life. Eric Jordan (E.J.) Wells’ goal is to become a hub for where entertainment professionals go to get their equipment and personnel to make their dream a reality, more than just a rental shop Wells also focuses on human relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Yolanda Massey</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/02/people-of-prosperus-yolanda-massey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/02/people-of-prosperus-yolanda-massey/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Yolanda Massey By: Weyman Cohen Hooked on Books, owned by Yolanda Massey, is a childcare service. During the year Massey provides childcare for younger children, mostly between the ages of five to seven (infants as well), but during the summer older children, (ages eight to ten) commonly attend Hooked on Books. Massey officially opened her childcare services in 2015. She is currently converting to a brick and mortar building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Gregory Carr</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/26/people-of-prosperus-gregory-carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 13:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/26/people-of-prosperus-gregory-carr/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Gregory Carr By: Weyman Cohen Gregory Carr, owner of Tall Greg Art, creates fine art for individuals as well as businesses. Tall Greg Art also offers classes to private individuals as well as art therapy for senior living facilities. Carr received a bachelor of arts from the College For Creative Studies with a major in illustration. From there, he ventured into commercial art, hoping to do creative advertisements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Annette Jordan</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/19/people-of-prosperus-annette-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 12:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/19/people-of-prosperus-annette-jordan/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Annette Jordan By: Anna Gotskind Annette Jordan, founder of Goddess Life Botanicals, is a registered nurse and herbalist striving to help people be healthier through a variety of original products including several types of herbs, oils, and supplements. Annette Jordan founded her company, Goddess Life Botanicals, after working with an herbalist and witnessing the healing powers of holistic medicine. At the time, Jordan had already been working as a registered nurse for many years and because of her medical training, she understood what illness is like and what recovery should look like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Shavonne Moorer</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/11/people-of-prosperus-shavonne-moorer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 15:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/11/people-of-prosperus-shavonne-moorer-2/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Shavonne Moorer By: Weyman Cohen Everlasting Collection, owned by Shavonne Moorer, is a women’s boutique that sells locally-made natural candles, handmade jewelry and custom t-shirts. Everlasting Collection strives to build confidence in all women by complimenting their unique style with trendy fashion, accessories &amp;amp; natural candles. Moorer places her focus on women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment, community-based organizations on equality, opportunities, networking, and business development with quality customer satisfaction.
Moorer’s enamoration with accessories started early on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Scheherazade Berry-Huff</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/06/people-of-prosperus-scheherazade-berry-huff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/06/people-of-prosperus-scheherazade-berry-huff/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Scheherazade Berry-Huff By: Weyman Cohen Luxe Skin Therapy is a holistic spa-inspired skin care line that is infused with elements of gold and silver minerals owned by Scheherazade Berry-Huff. Luxe Skin Therapy sells therapeutic products infused with minerals and skin care based on the alchemy of elements. Minerals can be used to treat problematic skin conditions (such as psoriasis, a condition that Scheherazade suffered from). Much of Luxe Skin Therapy’s clientele are people looking for remedies and treatments for various skin conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
