<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneur Showcase on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/entrepreneur-showcase/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneur Showcase on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:55:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/entrepreneur-showcase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2018 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for the annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
The event is generously supported by Quicken Loans and Fifth Third Bank.
5:30-7 PM: ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Showcase &amp;amp; Strolling Dinner 7-8:30 PM: Annual Convening Celebration Event Highlights:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Fall Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for a fall celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. We had an incredible time hosting entrepreneurs, community stakeholders, and advocates at this year&amp;rsquo;s annual event, so we wanted to create another opportunity for our partners and participants to come together and celebrate. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for an annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. This year, we&amp;rsquo;re especially excited to host a pitch competition sponsored by Fifth Third Bank following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
Details: May 11, 2017, from 5-8 PM The Jam Handy 2900 E. Grand Blvd. Detroit, MI 48202</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
