<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guide on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/categories/guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guide on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:32:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/categories/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shop Small in Detroit - 2018 Holiday Shopping Ideas</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/11/16/shop-small-in-detroit-2018-holiday-shopping-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/11/16/shop-small-in-detroit-2018-holiday-shopping-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Growing our neighborhoods and our communities takes all of us! Join ProsperUS Detroit in supporting local entrepreneurs this holiday season. In this list, you will find events hosted by community partners and neighborhood groups supporting ProsperUS Grads. If you have an event you&amp;rsquo;d like to add to our list, please let us know! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll support your neighbors with your shopping this season (and all year!).
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to share the excitement with #ShopSmallDetroit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Care of Kiddos; Taking Care of Business - Summer 2018</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/26/taking-care-of-kiddos-taking-care-of-business-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/26/taking-care-of-kiddos-taking-care-of-business-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>For many ProsperUS Detroit Grads and participants, being an entrepreneur is as much about what you are all building for yourselves as it is about what you&amp;rsquo;re building for your families and communities in the future. An issue this brings up is: how do entrepreneurs balance having a family and building a business? This issue is magnified when school is out for the summer and the issues of extended childcare become even more urgent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Two More Information Sessions for Winter 2017 Classes!</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 21:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</guid>
      <description>Come out to get details about our Entrepreneur Training Program: January 23, 2017
Grand River WorkPlace 19120 Grand River Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Larissa Carr – 313.437.3116 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17
January 24, 2017
Eastside Community Network 4401 Conner St. Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Suzanne Cleague – 313.571.2800 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17 You may also apply online HERE or **Download the fillable application HERE ** Applications are still being accepted at all of our training locations:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Small with ProsperUS Detroit: Holiday Season 2016</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/11/shop-small-with-prosperus-detroit-holiday-season-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/11/shop-small-with-prosperus-detroit-holiday-season-2016/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS November Networking Night Thursday, November 17, 2016, at 5:30 - 7:30 PM Vista Partnership / St. Anthony&amp;rsquo;s Church, 3555 Vernor Hwy, Detroit, MI 48216 Join the ProsperUS team for our monthly networking event for Graduates, current participants, prospective students, and friends! We will be featuring authentic Salvadoran cuisine from Cecilia Ardon of Bendicion de Dios and Juan Carlos from Featherstone Moments will do a presentation on revenue-generating &amp;ldquo;Holiday Marketing Ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
