<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 16:54:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Words of an Entrepreneur: Barbara Luna</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/23/words-of-entrepreneur-barbara-luna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/23/words-of-entrepreneur-barbara-luna/</guid>
      <description>My name is Barbara Luna. My husband, Jon, and I own 2 businesses. I am founder of 501c3 nonprofit Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Neighborhood Comeback Development. Our mission is to rebuild underserved communities to empower, educate and foster economic growth. We rehab houses a block at a time.
Currently, we have 3 houses being rehabbed to do supportive housing for homeless female veterans on a street we have had many social achievements on (such as starting a block group, repaving the street, starting a community garden, planting 20 trees, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flagstar Grant Winners</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/18/flagstar-grant-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 17:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/18/flagstar-grant-winners/</guid>
      <description>Flagstar Grant Winners
Many congratulations to the Flagstar Bank Grant winners! We are happy to know that you are among the 18 small businesses owned by people of color that will receive the $5,000 grant. We hope this brings you relief and some peace to this holiday season. While we are proud to be working to support small businesses, now more than ever, we also recognize that this is part of a much bigger problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Lesa Walker</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/27/people-of-prosperus-lesa-walker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/27/people-of-prosperus-lesa-walker/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Lesa Walker By: Torisa Johnson  Lesa Walker grew up in Canada, and has lived in Detroit for her adult life. Growing up in a large family with nine siblings, Walker spent lots of quality time early in life experimenting with deserts and competing against her siblings. Walker’s fond memories of making cow patties alongside them influenced the name of her business, Sweet Thoughts. Appropriately named, Sweet Thoughts is a dessert business selling various forms of delicious chocolate and dessert chips, additionally offering healthy yet sweet options that still manage to be delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US in the News: ProsperUS Entrepreneur Jennifer Lyle featured in O Magazine!</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/us-in-the-news-prosperus-entrepreneur-jennifer-lyle-featured-in-o-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/us-in-the-news-prosperus-entrepreneur-jennifer-lyle-featured-in-o-magazine/</guid>
      <description>US in the News: ProsperUS Entrepreneur Jennifer Lyle featured in O Magazine! Congratulations to Jennifer Lyle, owner of Lush Yummy Pie Co., who was recently featured in O Magazine&amp;rsquo;s A Guide to the 50 Black-Owned and Created Businesses on Oprah&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Favorite Things List for her Peach Butta Cobbler. It brings us so much joy to see ProsperUS entrepreneurs achieving wide recognition for their successes! Check out where you can try one of your own delicious Lush Yummy pies here, and read the full list in O Magazine here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Enid Parham</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/people-of-prosperus-enid-parham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 18:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/people-of-prosperus-enid-parham/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Enid Parham By: Torisa Johnson A chef all of her life, Detroit native Enid Parham puts a twist on food by combining her passion for cooking with her love for cannabis. After lots of careful research on the topic, including testing groups, Parham started her business, Lucky Pistil, in 2016. Lucky Pistil is a far cry from traditional cannabis edibles found in dispensaries. Parham’s dishes and catering services are gourmet dishes with up-scale food and service, though she does offer the option of casual settings as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Lea Addington</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/13/people-of-prosperus-lea-addington/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 19:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/13/people-of-prosperus-lea-addington/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Lea Addington By: Mackenzie Hewitt  Born and raised in metro-Detroit, Lea Addington began her business, LIT Vegan Kitchen, in 2017. Addington had been vegan for several months when one of her family members reached out to her seeking help transitioning their diet due to medical reasons. After Addington began to notice the positive changes as a result of her vegan diet, she decided to share this with her community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US in the News: &#34;Community Leans in to Help Detroit Ice Cream Entrepreneur Through COVID-19&#34;</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/13/us-in-the-news-community-leans-in-to-help-detroit-ice-cream-entrepreneur-through-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/13/us-in-the-news-community-leans-in-to-help-detroit-ice-cream-entrepreneur-through-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>US in the News: &amp;ldquo;Community Leans in to Help Detroit Ice Cream Entrepreneur Through COVID-19&amp;rdquo; Model D Media We are always happy to share the achievements of ProsperUS entrepreneurs. Congratulations to KaToya Scott, owner of Junk Food and Friends, who was recently featured in model D media!
Read the full story here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US in the News: &#34;Detroit nonprofits collaborate to launch equitable economic development program&#34;</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/06/us-in-the-news-detroit-nonprofits-collaborate-to-launch-equitable-economic-development-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/06/us-in-the-news-detroit-nonprofits-collaborate-to-launch-equitable-economic-development-program/</guid>
      <description>US in the News: &amp;ldquo;Detroit nonprofits collaborate to launch equitable economic development program&amp;rdquo; Model D Media It brings us joy when the community acknowledges our entrepreneurs for their successes! Congratulations to Harriette Brown, owner of Sisters on a Roll, who was featured in Model D Media.
Read the full story here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Mayra Planas</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/06/people-of-prosperus-mayra-planas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/06/people-of-prosperus-mayra-planas/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Mayra Planas By: Torisa Johnson Mayra Planas moved from Miami to Detroit with her family in 2002. Born and raised in Cuba, Miami resembled home in language and climate, but Detroit was a completely different scene. Planas tried to go back to Miami for two years, but in the end was glad she stayed, as she developed a love for both the city and the people. The idea to start her company, Havana on Wheels, came to Planas in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flagstar Black, Indigenous, and People of Color Grant Program</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/02/flagstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 22:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/02/flagstar/</guid>
      <description>Flagstar Black, Indigenous, and People of Color Grant Guidelines  ProsperUS Detroit is partnering with Flagstar Bank to provide grants to small businesses in Detroit, Michigan.  WINNERS ANNOUCED! Congratulations to the winners of the Flagstar Grants! The winners are listed here:
Jerome B. Brown &amp;amp; Samuel Van Buren, Detroit Soul
Angel Fuller, Angel&amp;rsquo;s Kiddie Kingdom Learning Center
Kelly Bishaw, Lovin&#39; Touch Learning Center
Jonathan Merritt, Narrow Way Café
Marlene Brooks, Dymond Designs Beauty School</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Le’Genevieve Squires &amp; Brittiany Peeler</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/30/people-of-prosperus-legenevieve-squires-brittiany-peeler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 21:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/30/people-of-prosperus-legenevieve-squires-brittiany-peeler/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Le’Genevieve Squires &amp;amp; Brittiany Peeler  By: Mackenzie Hewitt Detroit natives Brittiany Peeler and Le’Genevieve Squires formalized their business, Experience Relish, in 2018. After attending college, the pair moved backed to Detroit in 2016. At the time, Experience Relish was only a hobby that involved cooking for family and friends, but their fresh take on childhood dishes began to spread quickly by word of mouth. They decided to gain knowledge about becoming a catering company, and they attended Detroit Start-Up Week and Skill Share Classes at FoodLab that same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Whitney &amp; Jeremy Lewis</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/23/people-of-prosperus-whitney-jeremy-lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 18:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/23/people-of-prosperus-whitney-jeremy-lewis/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Whitney and Jeremy Lewis By Mackenzie Hewitt Whitney and Jeremy Lewis were both born and raised in Detroit, MI, and returned in 2016 after leaving temporarily for college. Two foodies with a drive for entrepreneurship, the couple launched Boiling Point Detroit in 2019, inspired by the unique dining experience of a seafood boil. After cooking for family and friends initially, the couple branched out to host events. When their service was well received by the public, they knew Boiling Point would take off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of Prosper US: Germaine Jordan and Fatima Fleming</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/13/people-of-prosper-us-germaine-jordan-and-fatima-fleming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 14:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/13/people-of-prosper-us-germaine-jordan-and-fatima-fleming/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Germain Jordan and Fatima Fleming By: Torisa Johnson Germaine Jordan and Fatima Fleming started their journey working in the food industry around the same time they began their journey as partners in life. Running a business and planning a wedding at the same time wasn’t easy, Jordan recalls doing a few events rather than working full time when starting up in 2017. Once their business, Blu VI Catering, legally formalized it took off quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Jamie Hendrix</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/01/people-of-prosperus-jamie-hendrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 17:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/10/01/people-of-prosperus-jamie-hendrix/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Jamie Hendrix By: Anna Gotskind BeHer is a women’s clothing store that offers a variety of tops, bottoms, one-pieces, and dresses in sizes ranging from small to plus-sized. Based in Morningside Detroit, BeHer specializes in urban street style and transitional all-day wear allowing customers to wear the pieces both to work as well as any evening event after.
 Jamie Hendrix, the founder of BeHer, started out wanting to restore a storefront in her community of Morningside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Simmons Family</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/25/people-of-prosperus-simmons-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 16:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/25/people-of-prosperus-simmons-family/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: The Simmons Family By: Weyman Cohen Tag Team Autoworks is a collision shop specializing in detailing. Tag Team Autoworks (TTA) has an office that does government contracts. There is a division of the business that goes into housing and urban development. **The Simmons family mission **is to get the collision shop up and running. Gerald, having suffered dozens of heart attacks, serves his family as a teacher of business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Shayla Davis</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/15/people-of-prosperus-shayla-davis-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 16:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/15/people-of-prosperus-shayla-davis-2/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Shayla Davis By: Anna Gotskind Unik I Am strives to empower and uplift young women to embrace their journey and not let mistakes define who they are. Founder, Shayla Davis, accomplishes this through motivational speaking about her own experiences and providing support services to help women find housing, jobs, and more.
Unik I Am&amp;rsquo;s mission is to seek to uplift, empower, and motivate women to understand and embrace their struggles, success, failures, mistakes, and achieve their goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: E.J. Wells</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/08/people-of-prosperus-e-j-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 18:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/08/people-of-prosperus-e-j-wells/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: E.J. Wells By: Weyman Cohen LightsUp Entertainment’s mission is to provide quality and personal production value to your event using lighting, sound and production professionals to make your vision come to life. Eric Jordan (E.J.) Wells’ goal is to become a hub for where entertainment professionals go to get their equipment and personnel to make their dream a reality, more than just a rental shop Wells also focuses on human relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Yolanda Massey</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/02/people-of-prosperus-yolanda-massey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/09/02/people-of-prosperus-yolanda-massey/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Yolanda Massey By: Weyman Cohen Hooked on Books, owned by Yolanda Massey, is a childcare service. During the year Massey provides childcare for younger children, mostly between the ages of five to seven (infants as well), but during the summer older children, (ages eight to ten) commonly attend Hooked on Books. Massey officially opened her childcare services in 2015. She is currently converting to a brick and mortar building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Gregory Carr</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/26/people-of-prosperus-gregory-carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 13:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/26/people-of-prosperus-gregory-carr/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Gregory Carr By: Weyman Cohen Gregory Carr, owner of Tall Greg Art, creates fine art for individuals as well as businesses. Tall Greg Art also offers classes to private individuals as well as art therapy for senior living facilities. Carr received a bachelor of arts from the College For Creative Studies with a major in illustration. From there, he ventured into commercial art, hoping to do creative advertisements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Annette Jordan</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/19/people-of-prosperus-annette-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 12:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/19/people-of-prosperus-annette-jordan/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Annette Jordan By: Anna Gotskind Annette Jordan, founder of Goddess Life Botanicals, is a registered nurse and herbalist striving to help people be healthier through a variety of original products including several types of herbs, oils, and supplements. Annette Jordan founded her company, Goddess Life Botanicals, after working with an herbalist and witnessing the healing powers of holistic medicine. At the time, Jordan had already been working as a registered nurse for many years and because of her medical training, she understood what illness is like and what recovery should look like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Shavonne Moorer</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/11/people-of-prosperus-shavonne-moorer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 15:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/11/people-of-prosperus-shavonne-moorer-2/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Shavonne Moorer By: Weyman Cohen Everlasting Collection, owned by Shavonne Moorer, is a women’s boutique that sells locally-made natural candles, handmade jewelry and custom t-shirts. Everlasting Collection strives to build confidence in all women by complimenting their unique style with trendy fashion, accessories &amp;amp; natural candles. Moorer places her focus on women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment, community-based organizations on equality, opportunities, networking, and business development with quality customer satisfaction.
Moorer’s enamoration with accessories started early on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Scheherazade Berry-Huff</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/06/people-of-prosperus-scheherazade-berry-huff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/08/06/people-of-prosperus-scheherazade-berry-huff/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Scheherazade Berry-Huff By: Weyman Cohen Luxe Skin Therapy is a holistic spa-inspired skin care line that is infused with elements of gold and silver minerals owned by Scheherazade Berry-Huff. Luxe Skin Therapy sells therapeutic products infused with minerals and skin care based on the alchemy of elements. Minerals can be used to treat problematic skin conditions (such as psoriasis, a condition that Scheherazade suffered from). Much of Luxe Skin Therapy’s clientele are people looking for remedies and treatments for various skin conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Olivia  Croom</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/17/people-of-prosperus-olivia-croom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/17/people-of-prosperus-olivia-croom/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Olivia Croom By: Anna Gotskind “I am a dentist by training and had my own practice for a number of years. I sold it and started working for a large dental organization that treated the underserved population.
When Olivia Croom, one of the co-founders of Dancing Zebras, began treating children from low-income families she quickly discovered that many of them had substantial tooth decay.
Inspired, Croom went home and decided she would find a way to address this problem herself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Hiring: Program Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/16/were-hiring-program-coordinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 14:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/16/were-hiring-program-coordinator/</guid>
      <description>Link to apply:
http://www.swsol.org/jobs/?gnk=job&amp;amp;gni=8a78879e7239c8240172ccfd3762712b
Program Coordinator Full-Time/Hourly
Reports to Program Manager
POSITION SUMMARY****: The Program Coordinator works with ProsperUS Detroit and its partners to provide administrative support and to coordinate aspects of the entrepreneur training program. Daily functions include but are not limited to program administration, executive assistance, outreach and communication to program participants and partners, event planning and implementation, and other responsibilities as assigned. The role requires flexibility in schedule, with evening hours periodically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request for Proposal: Construction Advisor</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/10/request-for-proposal-construction-advisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/10/request-for-proposal-construction-advisor/</guid>
      <description>Work with ProsperUS Detroit-supported businesses on planning and managing build out of their commercial spaces, all the way to Certificate of Occupancy/Acceptance.
SUMMARY The Construction Advisor (CA) consults Detroit neighborhood business owners on behalf of ProsperUS Detroit on a contractual basis. The CA&amp;rsquo;s tasks include:
 * Assessment of and action planning with business owners on zoning compliance, land use, and prioritization of property needs * Review and provide feedback on architectural plans and engineering documents * Review, vet, and provide feedback on contractor proposals and scopes of work * Identification and direct assistance in applying for necessary permits  when needed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Candice Meeks</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/09/people-of-prosperus-candice-meeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/09/people-of-prosperus-candice-meeks/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Candice Meeks By Weyman Cohen Candice Meeks started theCraft Cafe as a place to create. The Cafe hosts art parties (10 or less people during COVID) including canvas and wine glass painting, vision boards and mirrors and private space rental for any occasion. Homemade art kits are also sold: five pre-sketched canvases, paint, brushes and instructions on how to paint the picture. Meeks started her entrepreneurial journey when she was still working as a business consultant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Tamarra Glenn</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/07/people-of-prosperus-tamarra-glenn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/07/people-of-prosperus-tamarra-glenn/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Tamarra Glenn By: Anna Gotskind Tamarra Glenn, the founder of Khamilion Kafe, began as a regular nail technician. When a few customers began coming in and requesting medical accommodations to their service most of the nail techs were not interested and did not know what to do. Glenn decided to make it her responsibility to learn about how to treat these clients safely. She discovered that in many cases alterations did need to be made for clients with different illnesses and Glenn taught herself how to treat them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Laura Alvarado</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/07/people-of-prosperus-laura-alvarado/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/07/people-of-prosperus-laura-alvarado/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Laura Alvarado By: Anna Gotskind Laura Alvarado, the founder of Tropical Sweets Cakes, has been baking since she was thirteen years old.
Alvarado taught herself how to create beautiful custom cakes first in Puerto Rico and now she applies her skills here in Detroit.
Inspired by her aunt, Alvarado began baking more cakes and improving her skill. She discovered that, like her family, she had a talent for baking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Shavonne Moorer</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/07/people-of-prosperus-shavonne-moorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 16:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/07/people-of-prosperus-shavonne-moorer/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Shavonne Moorer By Weyman Cohen Everlasting Collection, owned by Shavonne Moorer, is a women’s boutique that sells locally-made natural candles, handmade jewelry and custom t-shirts. Everlasting Collection strives to build confidence in all women by complimenting their unique style with trendy fashion, accessories &amp;amp; natural candles. Moorer places her focus on women empowerment, community-based organizations on equality, opportunities, networking and business development with quality customer satisfaction. Moorer’s enamoration with accessories started early on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProsperUS Programs FAQ</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/prosperus-programs-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/prosperus-programs-faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions    1. General Questions 2. Entrepreneur Training Questions 3. Business Services Questions 4. Micro Lending Questions  General Questions What is ProsperUS?
ProsperUS Detroit is a place-based economic development strategy designed to empower low and moderate-income, immigrant, and minority individuals. Through our culturally competent range of services, we strive to support the entrepreneurial spirit and small business community that exists in Detroit’s neighborhoods.
What services does ProsperUS offer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Harriette Brown</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/02/people-of-prosperus-harriette-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/02/people-of-prosperus-harriette-brown/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Harriette Brown By Anna Gotskind Sisters on a Roll is a mobile cafe and catering company that strives to heal people with food. Harriette Brown (aka Chef Bee) specializes in customized menus to serve the community needs such as vegan/vegetarian, kosher, and halal.
“I come from outreach ministry. I’ve been cooking for people all my life. It’s my way of waging war with a fork. It’s my way of sharing love on a plate because I found that in feeding people I don’t have to speak your language to nourish you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProsperUS recruiting bilingual Spanish/English Trainer</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/17/prosperus-recruiting-bilingual-spanishenglish-trainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 16:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/17/prosperus-recruiting-bilingual-spanishenglish-trainer/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Training Program! We are looking for a bilingual Spanish/English instructor for the Entrepreneurship Training Program.  To apply send your resume and a brief letter of introduction to prosperus@swsol.org
 The Entrepreneur Training Program teaches business skills to adults. We actively recruit from under-resourced neighborhoods and assume participants have little to no business education. There is not a specific type of business that we support so we are looking for a candidate who is willing to work in-depth with individuals on a broad variety of businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS: Alison Heeres</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/16/covid-19-and-the-people-of-prosperus-alison-heeres/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 18:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/16/covid-19-and-the-people-of-prosperus-alison-heeres/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS: Alison Heeres Interview and Photography by Kenny Karpov Our business, Coriander Kitchen and Farm is located in the Jefferson-Chalmers neighborhood at 14610 Riverside Blvd. We’ve been developing a restaurant on the canals over there for about the last year. Our business normally is running a catering business that we’ve been expanding through this restaurant venture with the help of ProsperUS, DDF, Michigan Women’s Forward as well as Motor City Match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS: Lester Gouvia</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/12/covid-19-and-the-people-of-prosperus-lester-gouvia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 17:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/12/covid-19-and-the-people-of-prosperus-lester-gouvia/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS: Lester Gouvia Interview and Photography by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.prosperusdetroit.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Lester-full-interview.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
We’re a casual fine dining Caribbean restaurant in the Jefferson-Chalmers neighborhood. The area is historic. The building is historic. From what I was told I am the first sit-down restaurant in the area in 30 years. The construction on the building started in 2017, and then, in late 2018 the build-out was finished and we opened our doors to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS: Elisha Harrington</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/05/covid-19-and-the-people-of-prosperus-elisha-harrington/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/06/05/covid-19-and-the-people-of-prosperus-elisha-harrington/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS: Elisha Harrington Interview and Photography by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.prosperusdetroit.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Full-Interview-1.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
“I am one of the owners of Ella Mae’s Place, along with my son, who is the chef, and my brother and sister. We originally opened in the summer of 2008, and we ran the restaurant for five years. Then [we] had to shut down due to inspections that needed to be passed with the City of Detroit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS During COVID-19: Sterling Wise</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/28/people-of-prosperus-during-covid-19-sterling-wise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 19:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/28/people-of-prosperus-during-covid-19-sterling-wise/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 and the People of ProsperUS : Sterling Wise Interview and Photography by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.prosperusdetroit.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Sterling-Wise-Full-Interview.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
&amp;ldquo;I am Sterling Wise, owner of The Wise Decision, a health and fitness studio based in downtown Detroit. We offer an open gym style membership along with other fitness and health events outside the studio. &amp;ldquo;Honestly we were having our best year ever! Opening up 2020, the first two months were the best I’ve seen for our gym since I started running this business 13 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Shayla Davis</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/21/people-of-prosperus-shayla-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/21/people-of-prosperus-shayla-davis/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Shayla Davis Edited by Christiane Radford My name is Shayla Unik Davis, Human Resources director for an architecture firm and creator of _Unik I Am, LLC. _Finances are something I had to learn to take seriously. Once upon a time, due to poor decisions and mistakes, I was barely able to make ends meet. My personal trials inspired me to start a small business to help other young women in resume writing, tutoring, HR resources, and mentoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Yvette Jenkins</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/15/people-of-prosperus-yvette-jenkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 17:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/15/people-of-prosperus-yvette-jenkins/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Yvette Jenkins Interview and Photography by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.prosperusdetroit.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Full-Interview.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
“I am Yvette Jenkins of Love Travels Imports. We’re at 19452 Livernois, Detroit, MI, which is considered the Avenue of Fashion. We’ve been operating out of this location since 2013.
“This journey as an entrepreneur in this phase started back in 2010, when I was downsized from a corporate job. I am a lifelong Detroiter. In fact, I grew up here on the West-side of the city not far from where we are now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Ewanda Wyndella</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/07/people-of-prosperus-ewanda-wyndella/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 18:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/07/people-of-prosperus-ewanda-wyndella/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Ewanda Wyndella Interview and Photography by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.prosperusdetroit.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Ewanda-Full-interview.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
“My name is Ewanda Wyndella. I am 47-years-old and a single mom of five. “I grew up on the West side of Detroit, with my mom and dad. My dad eventually moved to Chicago and became a politician. So I am kind of an activist with a cultural background. I was raised African centered. When I was young, I was one of those girls caught in the hood and the community that wanted to do good, and do better by my community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Ali Badani</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/01/ali-badani/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 14:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/05/01/ali-badani/</guid>
      <description>People of ProsperUS: Ali Badani Interview and photography by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.prosperusdetroit.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/Full-Interview.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
“I’m from Yemen originally, and moved to Michigan in 1999 with my parents. I grew up in Hamtramck and went to school there. After graduating High School, I did two semesters of college at Henry Ford, and then I dropped out. It was boring for me, but I should have stayed to finish my degree. I then went into trucking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Monica Casarez</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/04/24/monica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/04/24/monica/</guid>
      <description>Remembering MONICA ECHEVERRI CASAREZ Our beloved trainer Monica Echeverri Casarez passed away Easter Sunday due to complications caused by Covid-19. Monica taught our Southwest Detroit cohorts and her entrepreneurs loved her for many reasons. We remember Monica as a bright energetic personality with a sharp mind. She was a woman who valued justice and took action to help others. She had a way to entertain and inspire and we loved hearing her stories and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statement on COVID-19 and additional resources</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/03/18/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/03/18/covid/</guid>
      <description>**_ _**Check back here for up to date information.
June 19, 2020 Update on COVID-19 As the state begins to allow businesses to reopen we urge you to make responsible decisions about what is in the best interest of your community and you personally. If your business is reopening the State of Michigan requires that you update your COVID-19 Preparedness &amp;amp; Response Plan.
Next Tuesday there is a hands on workshop on creating this plan available here: LINK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Craig Grissom</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/03/04/craig-grissom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 21:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/03/04/craig-grissom/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS is bringing back the &amp;ldquo;People of ProsperUS&amp;rdquo; series, highlighting the stories of the people we serve. This first interview features Craig Grissom, the owner of Higher Ground - a landscaping company. In this interview Craig discusses his struggles with the criminal justice system, journey into entrepreneurship, and how his faith helped sustain him. For his next business venture, Craig is opening a non-emergency medical transportation company.
People of ProsperUS: Craig Grissom Interview and photos by Kenny Karpov [audio mp3=&amp;ldquo;http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Small in Detroit - 2018 Holiday Shopping Ideas</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/11/16/shop-small-in-detroit-2018-holiday-shopping-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/11/16/shop-small-in-detroit-2018-holiday-shopping-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Growing our neighborhoods and our communities takes all of us! Join ProsperUS Detroit in supporting local entrepreneurs this holiday season. In this list, you will find events hosted by community partners and neighborhood groups supporting ProsperUS Grads. If you have an event you&amp;rsquo;d like to add to our list, please let us know! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll support your neighbors with your shopping this season (and all year!).
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to share the excitement with #ShopSmallDetroit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Care of Kiddos; Taking Care of Business - Summer 2018</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/26/taking-care-of-kiddos-taking-care-of-business-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/26/taking-care-of-kiddos-taking-care-of-business-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>For many ProsperUS Detroit Grads and participants, being an entrepreneur is as much about what you are all building for yourselves as it is about what you&amp;rsquo;re building for your families and communities in the future. An issue this brings up is: how do entrepreneurs balance having a family and building a business? This issue is magnified when school is out for the summer and the issues of extended childcare become even more urgent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply Now! Jump Start Your Retail Business Through Pop-Ups</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/18/apply-now-jump-start-your-retail-business-through-pop-ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/18/apply-now-jump-start-your-retail-business-through-pop-ups/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in ProsperUS Detroit&amp;rsquo;s new workshop series, a collaboration with Ebony Rutherford of Trish&amp;rsquo;s Garage. In this five-session course, serious retailers are encouraged to develop their merchandising, marketing, planning and customer service skill set with an experienced retail professional. Participants will become equipped with the necessary tools to start their own business or enhance an existing business through pop-ups.
Modules include: I. Hobby vs Business / Goal Setting II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request for Proposal: 5 Session Retail &#43; Merchandising Workshop Series</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/10/request-for-proposal-5-session-retail-merchandising-workshop-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 20:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/10/request-for-proposal-5-session-retail-merchandising-workshop-series/</guid>
      <description>Hello! ProsperUS Detroit is looking to launch a new workshop series focused on Retail + Merchandising to educate and empower participants for business in retail. Proposals should include a clearly defined subject and outcome.
The first ProsperUS Detroit workshop series of this kind was launch Fall of 2017 by Nick George of Dr. Sushi, a pop-up food consultant who guided participants through the process of planning, promoting, and presenting a pop-up food event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for the annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
The event is generously supported by Quicken Loans and Fifth Third Bank.
5:30-7 PM: ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Showcase &amp;amp; Strolling Dinner 7-8:30 PM: Annual Convening Celebration Event Highlights:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Fall Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for a fall celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. We had an incredible time hosting entrepreneurs, community stakeholders, and advocates at this year&amp;rsquo;s annual event, so we wanted to create another opportunity for our partners and participants to come together and celebrate. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Food Pop-up 101&#34; w/ Nick George of Dr. Sushi at Focus: HOPE</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/24/food-pop-up-101-w-nick-george-of-dr-sushi-at-focus-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/24/food-pop-up-101-w-nick-george-of-dr-sushi-at-focus-hope/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit&amp;rsquo;s new workshop series, a collaboration with Nick George of Dr. Sushi/Detroit Pop-Up Alliance, is a five session course, where serious food entrepreneurs are encouraged to develop their presentation, marketing, planning, and hospitality with an experienced chef and event planner. Participants will also be working alongside other intensely talented and passionate business owners in a spirit of learning and collaboration. The workshop series will take place at Focus: HOPE at 1400 Oakman Blvd, Detroit, MI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2017 ProsperUS Detroit Neighborhood Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/21/fall-2017-prosperus-detroit-neighborhood-office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/21/fall-2017-prosperus-detroit-neighborhood-office-hours/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit will be in your neighborhood soon! Two ProsperUS Detroit, staff members, Chris Butterfield, Small Business Advisor, and Amanda Brewington, Loan Officer, will be holding open office hours in our five geographies. The purpose of these office hours is to get us into the areas we serve and answer questions, start conversations and make access to our services even easier.
This is another chance to get on the spot answers to any of your business questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Jennifer Lyle, Lush Yummies Pie Co.</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/21/people-of-prosperus-jennifer-lyle-lush-yummies-pie-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/21/people-of-prosperus-jennifer-lyle-lush-yummies-pie-co/</guid>
      <description>This is the sixth post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Jennifer Lyle, the owner of Lush Yummies Pie Company.
“[My business is] Lush Yummies Pie Co. I sell pie; my signature pie is my Lemon “Butta” pie.”
ON STARTING A BUSINESS “I’ve always had an entrepreneurial spirit, I think. My grandmother started the first minority-owned business school in Detroit in 1973; it still stands today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Walter Winesberry, Maximize Autistic Potential</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/19/people-of-prosperus-walter-winesberry-maximize-autistic-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 14:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/19/people-of-prosperus-walter-winesberry-maximize-autistic-potential/</guid>
      <description>This is the fourth post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Walter Winesberry, the owner of Maximize Autistic Potential. “[My business is called] Maximize Autistic Potential. Over the last 11 years, through trial and error, we’ve come up with a completely natural protocol that diminishes autism symptoms in children. We’ve been helping families for about the last 10 years. I have a degree in biology which helps me look at what doctors and scientists are saying about what is happening in the bodies of children with autism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Nicole Scott, Cloudburst Visions</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/17/people-of-prosperus-nicole-scott-cloudburst-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 20:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/17/people-of-prosperus-nicole-scott-cloudburst-visions/</guid>
      <description>This is the third post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Nicole Scott, the owner of Cloudburst Visions Consulting.
“I have a social media marketing agency and my niche is restaurants and bars. I’m still in the early startup stages but I do a lot of prospecting. It is a lot of work, I’m usually reaching out to actual bars trying to get in touch [by contacting] decision makers: the business owner or general manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: JaTara Wright, Innovative Marketing Artistry</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/13/people-of-prosperus-jatara-wright-innovative-marketing-artistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/13/people-of-prosperus-jatara-wright-innovative-marketing-artistry/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features JaTara Wright, the owner, and creator of Innovative Marketing Artistry. “My business is Innovative Marketing Artistry. There are two parts to my business. We help small and medium-sized businesses position themselves effectively online to capture leads. [The other part is that] we empower individuals to work from home including students, disabled individuals, [etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chanell Scott Contreras is New ProsperUS Director</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/05/chanell-scott-contreras-is-new-prosperus-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/05/chanell-scott-contreras-is-new-prosperus-director/</guid>
      <description>Chanell Scott Contreras is the new director of Southwest Solutions’ ProsperUS Detroit program. Chanell takes over the role held by Kimberly Faison, who left to become program officer at the Ralph C. Wilson, Jr. Foundation. Kimberly had led ProsperUS since it began in 2012, and developed it into a premier program to train and support ethnic and immigrant entrepreneurs wanting to establish small businesses in Detroit neighborhoods.
“I am inspired by ProsperUS’ place-based approach to equitable economic development, and am honored and thrilled to join the ProsperUS team of talented and dedicated individuals who have an incredible track record of assisting aspiring small business owners in the city,” said Chanell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Daune Smith, Visual Noise</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/06/29/people-of-prosperus-daune-smith-visual-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 13:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/06/29/people-of-prosperus-daune-smith-visual-noise/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post in a series of photos titled, “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS Detroit.
Our first post features Daune Smith, owner and talented fashion designer for Visual Noise.
&amp;ldquo;My business is Visual Noise and I create a lineup of statement separates for women to wear assertively; it’s different from your normal wear. I’m always trying to come up with something new and different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap: 2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening and Pitch Competition</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/05/12/recap-2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-and-pitch-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/05/12/recap-2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-and-pitch-competition/</guid>
      <description>The ProsperUS Detroit team was thrilled by the outpouring of support and enthusiasm for the program and its entrepreneurs at its fifth annual event celebrating small businesses learning to grow in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Thanks to WillUParty Event Planning, Featherstone Moments for photographing the night, Three Lyons Creative for capturing video, Jam Handy for hosting, and to Fifth Third Bank for their generous financial support of the evening&amp;rsquo;s festivities!
  Photos courtesy of Juan Carlos Perez of Featherstone Moments:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for an annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. This year, we&amp;rsquo;re especially excited to host a pitch competition sponsored by Fifth Third Bank following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
Details: May 11, 2017, from 5-8 PM The Jam Handy 2900 E. Grand Blvd. Detroit, MI 48202</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources Landing</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/resources-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 14:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/resources-landing/</guid>
      <description>RESOURCE SECTIONS ProsperUS offers business owners support in a variety of areas. These resources are available to anyone in need of support. You do NOT need to be a loan recipient or entrepreneur training program participant to access these resources. For additional support check out our Business Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Two More Information Sessions for Winter 2017 Classes!</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 21:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</guid>
      <description>Come out to get details about our Entrepreneur Training Program: January 23, 2017
Grand River WorkPlace 19120 Grand River Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Larissa Carr – 313.437.3116 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17
January 24, 2017
Eastside Community Network 4401 Conner St. Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Suzanne Cleague – 313.571.2800 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17 You may also apply online HERE or **Download the fillable application HERE ** Applications are still being accepted at all of our training locations:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kecia Escoe:  A Socially Conscious Master Quilter</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/22/kecia-escoe-a-socially-conscious-master-quilter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/22/kecia-escoe-a-socially-conscious-master-quilter/</guid>
      <description>When Kecia Escoe applied to ProsperUs Detroit, she had recently left a human resources management position with her long-time employer, Ticketmaster. It was while completing her thesis for a master&amp;rsquo;s human resources program, when an emotional life event led to her discovery of her genetic talent for quilting. Although Kecia was pursuing human resources consulting, she chose to also pursue the ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Training Program at Focus: HOPE with trainer, Herb Drayton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katrina Taylor-Harris, Owner of First Step Children and Family Center</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/02/katrina-taylor-harris-owner-of-first-step-child-and-family-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/02/katrina-taylor-harris-owner-of-first-step-child-and-family-center/</guid>
      <description>Meet Katrina Taylor-Harris, someone we like to call a “Superstar.” In just over a year, she’s completed her Master in Social Work, completed the ProsperUS Detroit entrepreneur training class, secured a building for her daycare program, and closed on a micro-loan with ProsperUs. Her journey, to owning and operating First Step Children and Family Center, has been rare and unbelievably swift. It seems like just yesterday that our team was interviewing Katrina for a spot in one of the Focus: HOPE training cohorts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s an E-Commerce Investment Banker from Hong Kong Doing in Detroit?</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/21/whats-an-e-commerce-investment-banker-from-hong-kong-doing-in-detroit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 15:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/21/whats-an-e-commerce-investment-banker-from-hong-kong-doing-in-detroit/</guid>
      <description>Read full story here: What&amp;rsquo;s an E-Commerce Investment Banker from Hong Kong Doing in Detroit?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Small with ProsperUS Detroit: Holiday Season 2016</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/11/shop-small-with-prosperus-detroit-holiday-season-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/11/shop-small-with-prosperus-detroit-holiday-season-2016/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS November Networking Night Thursday, November 17, 2016, at 5:30 - 7:30 PM Vista Partnership / St. Anthony&amp;rsquo;s Church, 3555 Vernor Hwy, Detroit, MI 48216 Join the ProsperUS team for our monthly networking event for Graduates, current participants, prospective students, and friends! We will be featuring authentic Salvadoran cuisine from Cecilia Ardon of Bendicion de Dios and Juan Carlos from Featherstone Moments will do a presentation on revenue-generating &amp;ldquo;Holiday Marketing Ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pattern of Success: Detroit Garment Group helps entrepreneurs sew-up the market</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/03/a-pattern-of-success-detroit-garment-group-helps-entrepreneurs-sew-up-the-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 16:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/03/a-pattern-of-success-detroit-garment-group-helps-entrepreneurs-sew-up-the-market/</guid>
      <description>Read full story here: A Pattern of Success: Detroit Garment Group helps entrepreneurs sew-up the market</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Información en Español</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/informacion-en-espanol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 19:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/informacion-en-espanol/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit es una estrategia de desarrollo económico basado en el lugar diseñado para empoderar a las siguiente poblaciones: personas de ingresos bajos y moderados, los inmigrantes y minorías incluyendo sus barrios.
Lo Que Hacemos ENTRENAMIENTO DE EMPRESARIOS
 * Probada currículo de 12 capítulos que describe los pasos importantes para un exitoso plan de negocios * 12 sesiones interactivas incluyendo una graduación * 10 uno-a-uno sesiones con un profesional entrenador(a) culturalmente competente* * Plan de estudios escrito y enseñado en español  _* La competencia cultural se refiere a una forma en la cual uno respeta y honra los valores y creencias de individuos y familias de diferentes culturas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/corporate-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/corporate-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit is committed to collaboration as a tool of economic development for working with small businesses and entrepreneurs. Right now, we are developing packages to provide opportunities for corporations and established businesses to support entrepreneurs in our program. In the meantime, we are open to contributions and enthusiastic support from the community.
Examples of Ways to Help MONEY No matter what your company’s philanthropic budget is, you can make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Service Providers</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/business-service-providers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/business-service-providers/</guid>
      <description>Our Business Services program offers proven and professional services to neighborhood small businesses. These services build capacity for entrepreneurs and are high-quality, low-cost opportunities for growth.
The Business Services Program allows entrepreneurs to work in partnership with an awarded service provider and ProsperUS by reducing time and cost of key services. Those services are approved in an amount of hours determined by the Small Business Advisor, Business Services Committee, and the selected Service Provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/resources/</guid>
      <description>None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro-Lending</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/micro-lending/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/micro-lending/</guid>
      <description>The ProsperUS Detroit Lending Program provides access to capital for start-up and existing small businesses that otherwise might not have access with traditional sources. ProsperUS Detroit provides financing up to $50,000 for business located in Detroit.
Who We Serve ProsperUS takes an individualized approach to lending, working closely with entrepreneurs to understand their business needs, their long-term plans to grow and improve their business, the risks associated with their request, and the strategies they have in place to lessen those risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Services</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/business-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/business-services/</guid>
      <description>The main focus for any entrepreneur is the day-to-day operation of the business. ProsperUS celebrates that by assisting entrepreneurs when specific needs arise through our Business Services Program. Our team offers support by providing access to a network of professional service providers and collaborating to enhance business viability. For ProsperUS, Business Services include professional, trainer, and ProsperUS Detroit staff assistance in the areas of Accounting, Bookkeeping, Commercial Real Estate, Graphic Design, Human Resources, Legal, Marketing, Website Development, Food Consulting, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneur Training</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/entrepreneur-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/entrepreneur-training/</guid>
      <description>Applications for Spring 2021 are open until January 31st! Application available here. Solicitud para el Programa de Entrenamiento Empresarial In light of best practices regarding COVID-19 interviews and classes will be held via Zoom for all 2020 and potentially 2021. The ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Training program utilizes a place-based focus to economic development. In collaboration with Community Partners in specific areas in the city seen as having barriers to economic development and stability, we offer a comprehensive, 15-week entrepreneur training program that helps participants realize their potential, develop a business plan, and get their business off the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programs &amp; Services</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/programs-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/programs-services/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit is a place-based economic development strategy designed to empower low and moderate income, immigrant and minority individuals and neighborhoods. We offer a variety of services in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods to empower small business owners to become community leaders and advocates.
ENTREPRENEUR TRAINING
 * A proven, 12 chapter curriculum outlining the important steps to a successful business plan * 12 interactive classroom sessions including a graduation * 10 one-on-one sessions with a culturally competent, professional trainer * Curriculum written and taught in Spanish when needed  BUSINESS SERVICES</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work With Us</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/work-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 15:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/work-with-us/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit is committed to collaboration as a tool of economic development for working with small businesses and entrepreneurs. We are grateful for the contribution of time, services, and financial support. This can include consultation, professional services, or volunteer opportunities with our participating entrepreneurs and small business owners.
We have several opportunities for involvement with ProsperUS Detroit, and we welcome contributions for the betterment of Entrepreneur Training, Business Services, and Micro-Lending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funders</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/funders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/funders/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit is only possible due to the generous support of the philanthropic community, including philanthropy and private companies. This support allows us to meet our mission of providing equitable, culturally appropriate programming to Detroit residents and in its neighborhoods. Philanthropy has also challenged us to develop a robust program evaluation that has allowed to us to: assess who is being served, what their barriers to access are, and to hear their ideas about solutions and innovations to removing those barriers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Providers</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/service-providers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 14:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/service-providers/</guid>
      <description>Our Business Services program includes professional, trainer, and ProsperUS Detroit staff assistance in the areas of Accounting, Commercial Real Estate, Graphic Design, Human Resources, Legal, Marketing, Website Development, and others where appropriate. Once the application process for Business Services is complete, the Small Business Advisor will advocate on behalf of the entrepreneur to ensure the best possible course of action for the entrepreneur to achieve their goals. Following the planning stage, an introductory meeting is scheduled between the entrepreneur, ProsperUS, and the service provider to discuss collaboration and scope of service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trainers</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/trainers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/trainers/</guid>
      <description>With diverse backgrounds and business experience, our Trainers are culturally competent and committed to helping entrepreneurs succeed. Each Trainer excels at helping entrepreneurs get from a dream or an idea to developing an exhaustive understanding of what it takes to be an entrepreneur. Through twelve in-class sessions and ten one-on-one consultations, our Trainers are committed to helping participants progress toward the creation of a business plan. With ongoing relationships and accountability, our Trainers are mentors and counselors to students and program graduates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for contacting ProsperUS Detroit, please select the aspect of the program that you would like to contact from the drop-down list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit is a place-based economic development strategy designed to empower low and moderate income, immigrant and minority individuals. Through place-based, culturally competent services, we strive to support the entrepreneurial spirit and small business community that exists in Detroit’s neighborhoods. We work to make an impact through Entrepreneur Training, Business Services, and Micro-Lending. We hope to develop long-term relationships with Community Partners and entrepreneurs that will develop neighborhood leaders bolstering economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProsperUS Staff</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/prosperus-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 02:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/prosperus-staff/</guid>
      <description>Chanell Scott Contreras, Executive Director of ProsperUS Driven by her empathetic nature and passion for entrepreneurs of color, Chanell is deeply committed to increasing economic equity throughout Detroit. As the Executive Director of ProsperUS, she collaborates with a rich network of partners to strategically grow and develop training, business services, and microlending for underserved entrepreneurs in Detroit’s neighborhoods.
Prior to joining ProsperUS, Chanell worked on a range of community and economic development initiatives with organizations such as Kiva in Detroit and the Evergreen Cooperatives in Cleveland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Partners</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/community-partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/community-partners/</guid>
      <description>Working with Community Partners is central to the work that ProsperUS Detroit does in the city. Providing place-based, cultural understanding and establishing trust in the neighborhoods, our Community Partners are crucial to the success of our program and our entrepreneurs. We are always looking for ways to engage with and learn from the communities that we support through long-term relationships and offering wraparound services to those utilizing our program.
HOW COMMUNITY PARTNERS WORK WITH US</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit is a place-based economic development strategy designed to empower low and moderate income, immigrant and minority individuals. Through our culturally competent range of services, we strive to support the entrepreneurial spirit and small business community that exists in Detroit’s neighborhoods.
ENTREPRENEUR TRAINING Our training is about more than creating a business plan, it is about the introduction of solid business planning principles, network building, forming ideas and concepts, all combined with personal and professional development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 18:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/impact/</guid>
      <description>None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Black Journal:  Entrepreneurship in Detroit</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/09/18/american-black-journal-entrepreneurship-in-detroit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 14:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/09/18/american-black-journal-entrepreneurship-in-detroit/</guid>
      <description>None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metro Detroit entrepreneurial effort nets $2.9B impact</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/09/14/metro-detroit-entrepreneurial-effort-nets-2-9b-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 14:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/09/14/metro-detroit-entrepreneurial-effort-nets-2-9b-impact/</guid>
      <description>To read full article, click here: Metro Detroit entrepreneurial effort nets $2.9B impact</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProsperUS Detroit Stories</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/22/prosperus-detroit-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/22/prosperus-detroit-stories/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;iframe width=&amp;quot;560&amp;quot; allowfullscreen=&amp;quot;allowfullscreen&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries?list=PL3igXe0XQ_fUmu5TSDRoNXiF8bWauEbJz&amp;quot; frameborder=&amp;quot;0&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;315&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/iframe&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing Business And Community on Michigan Avenue in SW Detroit</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/15/growing-business-and-community-on-michigan-avenue-in-sw-detroit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 14:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/15/growing-business-and-community-on-michigan-avenue-in-sw-detroit/</guid>
      <description>To read full article, click here: Growing Business And Community on Michigan Avenue in SW Detroit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Super Instagram-Worthy Restaurants That Are Just As Delicious IRL</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/07/5-super-instagram-worthy-restaurants-that-are-just-as-delicious-irl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 14:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/07/5-super-instagram-worthy-restaurants-that-are-just-as-delicious-irl/</guid>
      <description>To read the full article, click here: 5 Super Instagram-Worthy Restaurants That Are Just As Delicious IRL</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Biz Stories: Amaze-EnJoyment with Antoine &amp; Collette Gulley</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/04/small-biz-stories-amaze-enjoyment-with-antoine-collette-gulley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 14:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/08/04/small-biz-stories-amaze-enjoyment-with-antoine-collette-gulley/</guid>
      <description>[embed]https://youtu.be/LosqJcrADTI[/embed]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voices from Impact Challange:  Harriette Brown &amp; Team 3</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/07/27/voices-from-impact-challange-harriette-brown-team-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/07/27/voices-from-impact-challange-harriette-brown-team-3/</guid>
      <description>To read full article, click here: Voices from Impact Challange: Harriette Brown &amp;amp; Team 3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 03:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/events/</guid>
      <description>None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Round 4 Motor City Match Announcements</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/07/20/motor-city-match-announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 17:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/07/20/motor-city-match-announcements/</guid>
      <description>To read the full article, click here: These 11 Detroit small business just won $500,000 in grants</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Biz Stories: Tiki&#39;s Treasures with Teresa Singleton</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/03/29/small-biz-stories-tikis-treasures-with-teresa-singleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 14:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/03/29/small-biz-stories-tikis-treasures-with-teresa-singleton/</guid>
      <description>[embed]https://youtu.be/u8_rG8QuddU[/embed]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProsperUs Detroit supports minority, immigrant small businesses</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/03/15/prosperus-detroit-supports-minority-immigrant-small-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/03/15/prosperus-detroit-supports-minority-immigrant-small-businesses/</guid>
      <description>To read the full article, click here: ProsperUs Detroit supports minority, immigrant small businesses</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lester Gouvia | Norma G&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/03/15/lester-gouvia-norma-gs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/03/15/lester-gouvia-norma-gs/</guid>
      <description>http://www.globaldetroit.com/stories/lester-gouvia/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imad Morad | My Computers and Phones</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2015/01/28/imad-morad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 19:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2015/01/28/imad-morad/</guid>
      <description>http://www.globaldetroit.com/stories/imad-agh-morad/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProsperUS Detroit  Annual Convening 2014</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2014/10/10/prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2014/10/10/prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-2014/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening 2014 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
