<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 18:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Words of an Entrepreneur: Barbara Luna</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/23/words-of-entrepreneur-barbara-luna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/23/words-of-entrepreneur-barbara-luna/</guid>
      <description>My name is Barbara Luna. My husband, Jon, and I own 2 businesses. I am founder of 501c3 nonprofit Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Neighborhood Comeback Development. Our mission is to rebuild underserved communities to empower, educate and foster economic growth. We rehab houses a block at a time.
Currently, we have 3 houses being rehabbed to do supportive housing for homeless female veterans on a street we have had many social achievements on (such as starting a block group, repaving the street, starting a community garden, planting 20 trees, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flagstar Grant Winners</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/18/flagstar-grant-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 17:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/12/18/flagstar-grant-winners/</guid>
      <description>Flagstar Grant Winners
Many congratulations to the Flagstar Bank Grant winners! We are happy to know that you are among the 18 small businesses owned by people of color that will receive the $5,000 grant. We hope this brings you relief and some peace to this holiday season. While we are proud to be working to support small businesses, now more than ever, we also recognize that this is part of a much bigger problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flagstar Black, Indigenous, and People of Color Grant Program</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/02/flagstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 22:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/02/flagstar/</guid>
      <description>Flagstar Black, Indigenous, and People of Color Grant Guidelines  ProsperUS Detroit is partnering with Flagstar Bank to provide grants to small businesses in Detroit, Michigan.  WINNERS ANNOUCED! Congratulations to the winners of the Flagstar Grants! The winners are listed here:
Jerome B. Brown &amp;amp; Samuel Van Buren, Detroit Soul
Angel Fuller, Angel&amp;rsquo;s Kiddie Kingdom Learning Center
Kelly Bishaw, Lovin&#39; Touch Learning Center
Jonathan Merritt, Narrow Way Café
Marlene Brooks, Dymond Designs Beauty School</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Hiring: Program Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/16/were-hiring-program-coordinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 14:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/07/16/were-hiring-program-coordinator/</guid>
      <description>Link to apply:
http://www.swsol.org/jobs/?gnk=job&amp;amp;gni=8a78879e7239c8240172ccfd3762712b
Program Coordinator Full-Time/Hourly
Reports to Program Manager
POSITION SUMMARY****: The Program Coordinator works with ProsperUS Detroit and its partners to provide administrative support and to coordinate aspects of the entrepreneur training program. Daily functions include but are not limited to program administration, executive assistance, outreach and communication to program participants and partners, event planning and implementation, and other responsibilities as assigned. The role requires flexibility in schedule, with evening hours periodically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Monica Casarez</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/04/24/monica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/04/24/monica/</guid>
      <description>Remembering MONICA ECHEVERRI CASAREZ Our beloved trainer Monica Echeverri Casarez passed away Easter Sunday due to complications caused by Covid-19. Monica taught our Southwest Detroit cohorts and her entrepreneurs loved her for many reasons. We remember Monica as a bright energetic personality with a sharp mind. She was a woman who valued justice and took action to help others. She had a way to entertain and inspire and we loved hearing her stories and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statement on COVID-19 and additional resources</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/03/18/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/03/18/covid/</guid>
      <description>**_ _**Check back here for up to date information.
June 19, 2020 Update on COVID-19 As the state begins to allow businesses to reopen we urge you to make responsible decisions about what is in the best interest of your community and you personally. If your business is reopening the State of Michigan requires that you update your COVID-19 Preparedness &amp;amp; Response Plan.
Next Tuesday there is a hands on workshop on creating this plan available here: LINK</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
