<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:27:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Jennifer Lyle, Lush Yummies Pie Co.</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/21/people-of-prosperus-jennifer-lyle-lush-yummies-pie-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/21/people-of-prosperus-jennifer-lyle-lush-yummies-pie-co/</guid>
      <description>This is the sixth post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Jennifer Lyle, the owner of Lush Yummies Pie Company.
“[My business is] Lush Yummies Pie Co. I sell pie; my signature pie is my Lemon “Butta” pie.”
ON STARTING A BUSINESS “I’ve always had an entrepreneurial spirit, I think. My grandmother started the first minority-owned business school in Detroit in 1973; it still stands today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Nicole Scott, Cloudburst Visions</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/17/people-of-prosperus-nicole-scott-cloudburst-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 20:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/17/people-of-prosperus-nicole-scott-cloudburst-visions/</guid>
      <description>This is the third post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Nicole Scott, the owner of Cloudburst Visions Consulting.
“I have a social media marketing agency and my niche is restaurants and bars. I’m still in the early startup stages but I do a lot of prospecting. It is a lot of work, I’m usually reaching out to actual bars trying to get in touch [by contacting] decision makers: the business owner or general manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: JaTara Wright, Innovative Marketing Artistry</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/13/people-of-prosperus-jatara-wright-innovative-marketing-artistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/13/people-of-prosperus-jatara-wright-innovative-marketing-artistry/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features JaTara Wright, the owner, and creator of Innovative Marketing Artistry. “My business is Innovative Marketing Artistry. There are two parts to my business. We help small and medium-sized businesses position themselves effectively online to capture leads. [The other part is that] we empower individuals to work from home including students, disabled individuals, [etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
