<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Detroit on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/detroit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Detroit on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:32:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/detroit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shop Small in Detroit - 2018 Holiday Shopping Ideas</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/11/16/shop-small-in-detroit-2018-holiday-shopping-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/11/16/shop-small-in-detroit-2018-holiday-shopping-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Growing our neighborhoods and our communities takes all of us! Join ProsperUS Detroit in supporting local entrepreneurs this holiday season. In this list, you will find events hosted by community partners and neighborhood groups supporting ProsperUS Grads. If you have an event you&amp;rsquo;d like to add to our list, please let us know! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll support your neighbors with your shopping this season (and all year!).
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to share the excitement with #ShopSmallDetroit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply Now! Jump Start Your Retail Business Through Pop-Ups</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/18/apply-now-jump-start-your-retail-business-through-pop-ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/18/apply-now-jump-start-your-retail-business-through-pop-ups/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in ProsperUS Detroit&amp;rsquo;s new workshop series, a collaboration with Ebony Rutherford of Trish&amp;rsquo;s Garage. In this five-session course, serious retailers are encouraged to develop their merchandising, marketing, planning and customer service skill set with an experienced retail professional. Participants will become equipped with the necessary tools to start their own business or enhance an existing business through pop-ups.
Modules include: I. Hobby vs Business / Goal Setting II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request for Proposal: 5 Session Retail &#43; Merchandising Workshop Series</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/10/request-for-proposal-5-session-retail-merchandising-workshop-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 20:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/10/request-for-proposal-5-session-retail-merchandising-workshop-series/</guid>
      <description>Hello! ProsperUS Detroit is looking to launch a new workshop series focused on Retail + Merchandising to educate and empower participants for business in retail. Proposals should include a clearly defined subject and outcome.
The first ProsperUS Detroit workshop series of this kind was launch Fall of 2017 by Nick George of Dr. Sushi, a pop-up food consultant who guided participants through the process of planning, promoting, and presenting a pop-up food event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/03/2018-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for the annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
The event is generously supported by Quicken Loans and Fifth Third Bank.
5:30-7 PM: ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Showcase &amp;amp; Strolling Dinner 7-8:30 PM: Annual Convening Celebration Event Highlights:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Fall Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/10/18/2017-prosperus-detroit-fall-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for a fall celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. We had an incredible time hosting entrepreneurs, community stakeholders, and advocates at this year&amp;rsquo;s annual event, so we wanted to create another opportunity for our partners and participants to come together and celebrate. Join us as we host an exciting pitch competition following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Food Pop-up 101&#34; w/ Nick George of Dr. Sushi at Focus: HOPE</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/24/food-pop-up-101-w-nick-george-of-dr-sushi-at-focus-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/24/food-pop-up-101-w-nick-george-of-dr-sushi-at-focus-hope/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit&amp;rsquo;s new workshop series, a collaboration with Nick George of Dr. Sushi/Detroit Pop-Up Alliance, is a five session course, where serious food entrepreneurs are encouraged to develop their presentation, marketing, planning, and hospitality with an experienced chef and event planner. Participants will also be working alongside other intensely talented and passionate business owners in a spirit of learning and collaboration. The workshop series will take place at Focus: HOPE at 1400 Oakman Blvd, Detroit, MI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2017 ProsperUS Detroit Neighborhood Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/21/fall-2017-prosperus-detroit-neighborhood-office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/21/fall-2017-prosperus-detroit-neighborhood-office-hours/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit will be in your neighborhood soon! Two ProsperUS Detroit, staff members, Chris Butterfield, Small Business Advisor, and Amanda Brewington, Loan Officer, will be holding open office hours in our five geographies. The purpose of these office hours is to get us into the areas we serve and answer questions, start conversations and make access to our services even easier.
This is another chance to get on the spot answers to any of your business questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Jennifer Lyle, Lush Yummies Pie Co.</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/21/people-of-prosperus-jennifer-lyle-lush-yummies-pie-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/21/people-of-prosperus-jennifer-lyle-lush-yummies-pie-co/</guid>
      <description>This is the sixth post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Jennifer Lyle, the owner of Lush Yummies Pie Company.
“[My business is] Lush Yummies Pie Co. I sell pie; my signature pie is my Lemon “Butta” pie.”
ON STARTING A BUSINESS “I’ve always had an entrepreneurial spirit, I think. My grandmother started the first minority-owned business school in Detroit in 1973; it still stands today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Walter Winesberry, Maximize Autistic Potential</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/19/people-of-prosperus-walter-winesberry-maximize-autistic-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 14:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/19/people-of-prosperus-walter-winesberry-maximize-autistic-potential/</guid>
      <description>This is the fourth post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Walter Winesberry, the owner of Maximize Autistic Potential. “[My business is called] Maximize Autistic Potential. Over the last 11 years, through trial and error, we’ve come up with a completely natural protocol that diminishes autism symptoms in children. We’ve been helping families for about the last 10 years. I have a degree in biology which helps me look at what doctors and scientists are saying about what is happening in the bodies of children with autism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Nicole Scott, Cloudburst Visions</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/17/people-of-prosperus-nicole-scott-cloudburst-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 20:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/17/people-of-prosperus-nicole-scott-cloudburst-visions/</guid>
      <description>This is the third post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features Nicole Scott, the owner of Cloudburst Visions Consulting.
“I have a social media marketing agency and my niche is restaurants and bars. I’m still in the early startup stages but I do a lot of prospecting. It is a lot of work, I’m usually reaching out to actual bars trying to get in touch [by contacting] decision makers: the business owner or general manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: JaTara Wright, Innovative Marketing Artistry</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/13/people-of-prosperus-jatara-wright-innovative-marketing-artistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/13/people-of-prosperus-jatara-wright-innovative-marketing-artistry/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS. This post features JaTara Wright, the owner, and creator of Innovative Marketing Artistry. “My business is Innovative Marketing Artistry. There are two parts to my business. We help small and medium-sized businesses position themselves effectively online to capture leads. [The other part is that] we empower individuals to work from home including students, disabled individuals, [etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chanell Scott Contreras is New ProsperUS Director</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/05/chanell-scott-contreras-is-new-prosperus-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/07/05/chanell-scott-contreras-is-new-prosperus-director/</guid>
      <description>Chanell Scott Contreras is the new director of Southwest Solutions’ ProsperUS Detroit program. Chanell takes over the role held by Kimberly Faison, who left to become program officer at the Ralph C. Wilson, Jr. Foundation. Kimberly had led ProsperUS since it began in 2012, and developed it into a premier program to train and support ethnic and immigrant entrepreneurs wanting to establish small businesses in Detroit neighborhoods.
“I am inspired by ProsperUS’ place-based approach to equitable economic development, and am honored and thrilled to join the ProsperUS team of talented and dedicated individuals who have an incredible track record of assisting aspiring small business owners in the city,” said Chanell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People of ProsperUS: Daune Smith, Visual Noise</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/06/29/people-of-prosperus-daune-smith-visual-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 13:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/06/29/people-of-prosperus-daune-smith-visual-noise/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post in a series of photos titled, “People of ProsperUS,” showcasing the incredible stories of entrepreneurs connected to ProsperUS Detroit.
Our first post features Daune Smith, owner and talented fashion designer for Visual Noise.
&amp;ldquo;My business is Visual Noise and I create a lineup of statement separates for women to wear assertively; it’s different from your normal wear. I’m always trying to come up with something new and different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/04/14/2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening/</guid>
      <description>Join the ProsperUS Detroit staff, our invaluable team of trainers, and our community partners for an annual celebration of place-based entrepreneurship in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. This year, we&amp;rsquo;re especially excited to host a pitch competition sponsored by Fifth Third Bank following a showcase and strolling dinner featuring many of our Entrepreneur Training Graduates and Participants.
Details: May 11, 2017, from 5-8 PM The Jam Handy 2900 E. Grand Blvd. Detroit, MI 48202</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Two More Information Sessions for Winter 2017 Classes!</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 21:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</guid>
      <description>Come out to get details about our Entrepreneur Training Program: January 23, 2017
Grand River WorkPlace 19120 Grand River Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Larissa Carr – 313.437.3116 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17
January 24, 2017
Eastside Community Network 4401 Conner St. Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Suzanne Cleague – 313.571.2800 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17 You may also apply online HERE or **Download the fillable application HERE ** Applications are still being accepted at all of our training locations:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kecia Escoe:  A Socially Conscious Master Quilter</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/22/kecia-escoe-a-socially-conscious-master-quilter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/22/kecia-escoe-a-socially-conscious-master-quilter/</guid>
      <description>When Kecia Escoe applied to ProsperUs Detroit, she had recently left a human resources management position with her long-time employer, Ticketmaster. It was while completing her thesis for a master&amp;rsquo;s human resources program, when an emotional life event led to her discovery of her genetic talent for quilting. Although Kecia was pursuing human resources consulting, she chose to also pursue the ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Training Program at Focus: HOPE with trainer, Herb Drayton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Small with ProsperUS Detroit: Holiday Season 2016</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/11/shop-small-with-prosperus-detroit-holiday-season-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/11/11/shop-small-with-prosperus-detroit-holiday-season-2016/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS November Networking Night Thursday, November 17, 2016, at 5:30 - 7:30 PM Vista Partnership / St. Anthony&amp;rsquo;s Church, 3555 Vernor Hwy, Detroit, MI 48216 Join the ProsperUS team for our monthly networking event for Graduates, current participants, prospective students, and friends! We will be featuring authentic Salvadoran cuisine from Cecilia Ardon of Bendicion de Dios and Juan Carlos from Featherstone Moments will do a presentation on revenue-generating &amp;ldquo;Holiday Marketing Ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
