<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Focus HOPE on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/focus-hope/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Focus HOPE on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 20:12:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/focus-hope/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Food Pop-up 101&#34; w/ Nick George of Dr. Sushi at Focus: HOPE</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/24/food-pop-up-101-w-nick-george-of-dr-sushi-at-focus-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/24/food-pop-up-101-w-nick-george-of-dr-sushi-at-focus-hope/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit&amp;rsquo;s new workshop series, a collaboration with Nick George of Dr. Sushi/Detroit Pop-Up Alliance, is a five session course, where serious food entrepreneurs are encouraged to develop their presentation, marketing, planning, and hospitality with an experienced chef and event planner. Participants will also be working alongside other intensely talented and passionate business owners in a spirit of learning and collaboration. The workshop series will take place at Focus: HOPE at 1400 Oakman Blvd, Detroit, MI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2017 ProsperUS Detroit Neighborhood Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/21/fall-2017-prosperus-detroit-neighborhood-office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/08/21/fall-2017-prosperus-detroit-neighborhood-office-hours/</guid>
      <description>ProsperUS Detroit will be in your neighborhood soon! Two ProsperUS Detroit, staff members, Chris Butterfield, Small Business Advisor, and Amanda Brewington, Loan Officer, will be holding open office hours in our five geographies. The purpose of these office hours is to get us into the areas we serve and answer questions, start conversations and make access to our services even easier.
This is another chance to get on the spot answers to any of your business questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Two More Information Sessions for Winter 2017 Classes!</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 21:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/01/09/information-sessions-for-winter-2017-classes-are-starting/</guid>
      <description>Come out to get details about our Entrepreneur Training Program: January 23, 2017
Grand River WorkPlace 19120 Grand River Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Larissa Carr – 313.437.3116 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17
January 24, 2017
Eastside Community Network 4401 Conner St. Detroit, MI 48215 6pm Contact: Suzanne Cleague – 313.571.2800 Application deadline: 5pm | 2.3.17 You may also apply online HERE or **Download the fillable application HERE ** Applications are still being accepted at all of our training locations:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kecia Escoe:  A Socially Conscious Master Quilter</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/22/kecia-escoe-a-socially-conscious-master-quilter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/22/kecia-escoe-a-socially-conscious-master-quilter/</guid>
      <description>When Kecia Escoe applied to ProsperUs Detroit, she had recently left a human resources management position with her long-time employer, Ticketmaster. It was while completing her thesis for a master&amp;rsquo;s human resources program, when an emotional life event led to her discovery of her genetic talent for quilting. Although Kecia was pursuing human resources consulting, she chose to also pursue the ProsperUS Detroit Entrepreneur Training Program at Focus: HOPE with trainer, Herb Drayton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katrina Taylor-Harris, Owner of First Step Children and Family Center</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/02/katrina-taylor-harris-owner-of-first-step-child-and-family-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2016/12/02/katrina-taylor-harris-owner-of-first-step-child-and-family-center/</guid>
      <description>Meet Katrina Taylor-Harris, someone we like to call a “Superstar.” In just over a year, she’s completed her Master in Social Work, completed the ProsperUS Detroit entrepreneur training class, secured a building for her daycare program, and closed on a micro-loan with ProsperUs. Her journey, to owning and operating First Step Children and Family Center, has been rare and unbelievably swift. It seems like just yesterday that our team was interviewing Katrina for a spot in one of the Focus: HOPE training cohorts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
