<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retail on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/retail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retail on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 13:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/retail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apply Now! Jump Start Your Retail Business Through Pop-Ups</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/18/apply-now-jump-start-your-retail-business-through-pop-ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/06/18/apply-now-jump-start-your-retail-business-through-pop-ups/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in ProsperUS Detroit&amp;rsquo;s new workshop series, a collaboration with Ebony Rutherford of Trish&amp;rsquo;s Garage. In this five-session course, serious retailers are encouraged to develop their merchandising, marketing, planning and customer service skill set with an experienced retail professional. Participants will become equipped with the necessary tools to start their own business or enhance an existing business through pop-ups.
Modules include: I. Hobby vs Business / Goal Setting II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request for Proposal: 5 Session Retail &#43; Merchandising Workshop Series</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/10/request-for-proposal-5-session-retail-merchandising-workshop-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 20:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2018/04/10/request-for-proposal-5-session-retail-merchandising-workshop-series/</guid>
      <description>Hello! ProsperUS Detroit is looking to launch a new workshop series focused on Retail + Merchandising to educate and empower participants for business in retail. Proposals should include a clearly defined subject and outcome.
The first ProsperUS Detroit workshop series of this kind was launch Fall of 2017 by Nick George of Dr. Sushi, a pop-up food consultant who guided participants through the process of planning, promoting, and presenting a pop-up food event.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
