<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lush Yummies Pie Co. on Prosper Us Detroit</title>
    <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/lush-yummies-pie-co./</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lush Yummies Pie Co. on Prosper Us Detroit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/tags/lush-yummies-pie-co./index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US in the News: ProsperUS Entrepreneur Jennifer Lyle featured in O Magazine!</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/us-in-the-news-prosperus-entrepreneur-jennifer-lyle-featured-in-o-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2020/11/21/us-in-the-news-prosperus-entrepreneur-jennifer-lyle-featured-in-o-magazine/</guid>
      <description>US in the News: ProsperUS Entrepreneur Jennifer Lyle featured in O Magazine! Congratulations to Jennifer Lyle, owner of Lush Yummy Pie Co., who was recently featured in O Magazine&amp;rsquo;s A Guide to the 50 Black-Owned and Created Businesses on Oprah&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Favorite Things List for her Peach Butta Cobbler. It brings us so much joy to see ProsperUS entrepreneurs achieving wide recognition for their successes! Check out where you can try one of your own delicious Lush Yummy pies here, and read the full list in O Magazine here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap: 2017 ProsperUS Detroit Annual Convening and Pitch Competition</title>
      <link>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/05/12/recap-2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-and-pitch-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prosperus-detroit-demo.com/2017/05/12/recap-2017-prosperus-detroit-annual-convening-and-pitch-competition/</guid>
      <description>The ProsperUS Detroit team was thrilled by the outpouring of support and enthusiasm for the program and its entrepreneurs at its fifth annual event celebrating small businesses learning to grow in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods. Thanks to WillUParty Event Planning, Featherstone Moments for photographing the night, Three Lyons Creative for capturing video, Jam Handy for hosting, and to Fifth Third Bank for their generous financial support of the evening&amp;rsquo;s festivities!
  Photos courtesy of Juan Carlos Perez of Featherstone Moments:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
